A Guide to the Hao Wang papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA274
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Office Files, 2
  - Harvard Correspondence, Marvin Lee Minsky (Box 13, Folder 317A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Miscellaenous (Box 13, Folder 318)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 318A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Edward F. Moore (Box 13, Folder 319)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Edward F. Moore (Box 13, Folder 319A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Ian B. Mueller (Box 14, Folder 320)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Ian B. Mueller (Box 14, Folder 320A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, N (Box 14, Folder 321)
  - Harvard Correspondence, K.S. Narendra (Box 14, Folder 322)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Alan Newell (Box 14, Folder 323)
  - Harvard Correspondence, O (Box 14, Folder 324)
  - Harvard Correspondence, John M. O'Connor (Box 14, Folder 325)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Ascher Opler (Box 14, Folder 326)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Charles Parsons (Box 14, Folder 327)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Charles Parsons (Box 14, Folder 327A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, M.O. Rabin (Box 14, Folder 328)
  - Harvard Correspondence, M.O. Rabin (Box 14, Folder 328A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Hartley Rogers (Box 14, Folder 329)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Hartley Rogers (Box 14, Folder 329A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, J. Barkley Rosser (Box 14, Folder 330)
  - Harvard Correspondence, S (Box 14, Folder 331)
  - Harvard Correspondence, G. Salton (Box 14, Folder 332)
  - Harvard Correspondence, G. Salton (Box 14, Folder 332A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Thomas M. Scanlon (Box 14, Folder 333)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Ralph Schoenman (Box 14, Folder 334)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Dana Scott (Box 14, Folder 335)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Dana Scott (Box 14, Folder 335A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, John Shepherdson (Box 14, Folder 336)
  - Harvard Correspondence, John Shepherdson (Box 14, Folder 336A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Ivan E. Sutherland (Box 14, Folder 337)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Ivan E. Sutherland (Box 14, Folder 337A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, T (Box 14, Folder 338)
  - Harvard Correspondence, T (Box 14, Folder 338A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Franklin D. Tall (Box 14, Folder 339)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Franklin D. Tall (Box 14, Folder 339A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Herbert M Teager (Box 14, Folder 340)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Stanley Tennenbaum (Box 14, Folder 341)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Stanley Tennenbaum (Box 14, Folder 341A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Frederick Thompson (Box 14, Folder 342)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Robert Tobey (Box 14, Folder 343)
  - Harvard Correspondence, John Torrey (Box 14, Folder 344)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Julius T. Tou (Box 14, Folder 345)
  - Harvard Correspondence, John Groff Truxal (Box 14, Folder 346)
  - Harvard Correspondence, J.W. Tucker (Box 14, Folder 347)
  - Harvard Correspondence, J.W. Tucker (Box 14, Folder 347A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Tom Tymoczko (Box 14, Folder 348)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Tom Tymoczko (Box 14, Folder 348A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, U (Box 14, Folder 349)
  - Harvard Correspondence, S.M. Ulam (Box 14, Folder 350)
  - Harvard Correspondence, University of Michigan (Box 14, Folder 351)
  - Harvard Correspondence, V (Box 14, Folder 352)
  - Harvard Correspondence, John van Heijenoort (Box 14, Folder 353)
  - Harvard Correspondence, John van Heijenoort (Box 14, Folder 353A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, W (Box 14, Folder 354)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Owen S. Walker (Box 14, Folder 355)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Robert L. Walton (Box 14, Folder 356)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Gary Yi-Chung Wang (Box 15, Folder 357)
  - Harvard Correspondence, John L. White (Box 15, Folder 358)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Maurice V. Wilkes (Box 15, Folder 359)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Eric Wolman (Box 15, Folder 360)
  - Harvard Correspondence, William W. Woods (Box 15, Folder 361)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Kuang Wu (Box 15, Folder 362)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Y (Box 15, Folder 363)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Edward Yu (Box 15, Folder 364)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Z (Box 15, Folder 365)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Z (Box 15, Folder 365A)
  - Harvard University and Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 366)
  - Harvard University, Long Range Planning Committee (Box 15, Folder 367)
  - Harvard University Society of Fellows (Box 15, Folder 368)
  - Zhao-wu He (Box 15, Folder 369)
  - Richard Herrnstein (Box 15, Folder 370)
  - Reuben Hersh, Includes: "To and From Philosophy - Discussions with Gödel and Wittgenstein" (Box 15, Folder 371)
  - Heyting (Box 15, Folder 372)
  - "Hilbert's First Problem: The Continuum Hypothesis" by Donald A. Martin (Box 15, Folder 373)
  - Jaako Hintikka (Box 15, Folder 374)
  - Xavier Hipp (Box 15, Folder 375)
  - Douglas Hofstadter (Box 15, Folder 376)
  - Mark Hogarth (Box 15, Folder 377)
  - Kai Hong (Box 15, Folder 378)
  - Kai Hong (Box 15, Folder 378A)
  - Jeremy Horne (Box 16, Folder 379)
  - William A. Howard (Box 16, Folder 380)
  - Karel Hrbacek (Box 16, Folder 381)
  - Karel Hrbacek (Box 16, Folder 381A)
  - Ray Huang (Box 16, Folder 382)
  - I (Box 16, Folder 383)
  - IBM (Box 16, Folder 384)
  - IBM, Bell Labs, Home Office, etc. (Box 16, Folder 385)
  - Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers (IEEE), Transactions on Computers (Box 16, Folder 386)
  - Nobuichi Ikeno (Box 16, Folder 387)
  - Income Tax (Box 16, Folder 388)
  - Institut Blaise Pascal (Box 16, Folder 389)
  - Institut für Mathematische Logik (Box 16, Folder 390)
  - Institute for Advanced Study (Box 16, Folder 391)
  - Institute "Vienna Circle" (Dr. Stadtler) (Box 16, Folder 392)
  - International Congress of Logic, Methodology and Philosophy of Science (Box 16, Folder 393)
  - International Symposium on Structures in Mathematical Theories (Box 16, Folder 394)
  - International Wittgenstein Symposia (Box 16, Folder 395)
  - Invitations - Declined (Box 16, Folder 396)
  - Invitations - Rejected, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 397)
  - National Institute for Research in Computer Science and Control (IRIA)(France) (Box 16, Folder 398)
  - Eugene Isaacson (Box 16, Folder 399)
  - IV Systems Symposium (Box 16, Folder 400)
  - J, K (Box 16, Folder 401)
  - R.L. Jean (Box 16, Folder 402)
  - Thomas Jech (Box 16, Folder 403)
  - Ronald Jensen (Box 16, Folder 404)
  - Jesus College, Cambridge, September 1-5, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 405)
  - Joint Program in Science and the Humanities, New York University and The Rockefeller University (Box 17, Folder 406)
  - Journal of Philosophical Logic (Box 17, Folder 407)
  - Journal of Philosophy (Box 17, Folder 408)
  - Journal of Symbolic Logic (Box 17, Folder 409)
  - Journals (Box 17, Folder 410)
  - Michael E. Jubien (Box 17, Folder 411)
  - Mark Kac (Box 17, Folder 412)
  - Hirokazu Kaneko (Box 17, Folder 413)
  - Jaan Kaplinski (Box 17, Folder 414)
  - I. Kapuano (Box 17, Folder 415)
  - Carol Karp (Box 17, Folder 416)
  - Alexander Kazakov (Box 17, Folder 417)
  - Alexander Kechris (Box 17, Folder 418)
  - Anne Kenny (Box 17, Folder 419)
  - Gyorgy Kepes (Box 17, Folder 420)
  - Kim and Sosa (Box 17, Folder 421)
  - D. King (Box 17, Folder 422)
  - Kirchberg, August 1991 (Box 17, Folder 423)
  - Philip Klahr (Box 17, Folder 424)
  - S.C. Kleene (Box 17, Folder 425)
  - Eugene M. Kleinberg (Box 17, Folder 426)
  - Eugene M. Kleinberg (Box 17, Folder 426A)
  - Kluwer Academic (Box 17, Folder 427)
  - Simon Kochen (Box 17, Folder 428)
  - Eckehart Köhler (and Gödel Society) (Box 17, Folder 429)
  - Gerhard F. Kohlmayr (Box 17, Folder 430)
  - Phokon Kolaitis (Box 17, Folder 431)
  - T. Komendziński (Box 17, Folder 432)
  - Ethan Kra (Box 17, Folder 433)
  - Albert A. Krassilov (Box 17, Folder 434)
  - Saul Kripke (Box 17, Folder 435)
  - Saul Kripke (Box 17, Folder 435A)
  - Kenneth Kunen (Box 17, Folder 436)
  - L (Box 17, Folder 437)
  - "L'Age de la Science" (Journal) (Box 18, Folder 438)
  - Lakatos (Box 18, Folder 439)
  - Rolf Landauer (Box 18, Folder 440)
  - Thomas N. Laurence (Box 18, Folder 441)
  - Jonathan Lear (Box 18, Folder 442)
  - Learned Socities, Degrees, Recommendations (Box 18, Folder 443)
  - Learned Socities, Degrees, Recommendations (Box 18, Folder 443A)
  - Joshua Lederberg (Box 18, Folder 444)
  - Gun-Won Lee (Box 18, Folder 445)
  - Daniel Leivant (Box 18, Folder 446)
  - Daniel Leivant (Box 18, Folder 446A)
  - L'Enseignement Mathematique (Box 18, Folder 447)
  - Wassily Leontief (Box 18, Folder 448)
  - Letters to be Sent Advising of Hao Wang's Death (Box 18, Folder 449)
  - Norman Levinson (Box 18, Folder 450)
  - Kuno Lorenz (Box 18, Folder 451)
  - Azriel Levy (Box 18, Folder 452)
  - You-Sheng Li (Box 18, Folder 453)
  - Library of Living Philosophers (Box 18, Folder 454)
  - "Library of Living Philosophers" - Quine (Box 18, Folder 455)
  - Per Lindström (Box 18, Folder 456)
  - L. Lipshitz (Box 18, Folder 457)
  - Logic Circle, New York University (Box 18, Folder 458)
  - Logic, "What is Logic?" Kirchberg, August 20, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 459)
  - London Review of Books, "Einstein and Gödel" (Box 19, Folder 460)
  - Lunatic Mail (Box 19, Folder 461)
  - M (Box 19, Folder 462)
  - Kenneth W. McAloon (Box 19, Folder 463)
  - Kenneth W. McAloon (Box 19, Folder 463A)
  - McGill University (Box 19, Folder 464)
  - Hiram McLandon (Box 19, Folder 465)
  - R. McNaughton (Box 19, Folder 466)
  - George McNulty (Box 19, Folder 467)
  - Mailing List (Box 19, Folder 468)
  - Miroslaw Majewski (Box 19, Folder 469)
  - J.A. Makowsky (Box 19, Folder 470)
  - David Malament (Box 19, Folder 471)
  - David Malament (Box 19, Folder 471A)
  - Larry Manevitz (Box 19, Folder 472)
  - Larry Manevitz (Box 19, Folder 472A)
  - Maps (Box 19, Folder 473)
  - Donald A. Martin (1 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 474)
  - Donald A. Martin (2 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 475)
  - Donald A. Martin (3 of 3) (Box 20, Folder 476)
  - Donald A. Martin (Box 20, Folder 476A)
  - Donald A. Martin, Vita and Publications List (Box 20, Folder 477)
  - Robert Martin (Box 20, Folder 478)
  - Bruno Martini (Box 20, Folder 479)
  - Matching Program (Box 20, Folder 480)
  - Materialism (Box 20, Folder 481)
  - "Mathematical Reviews" (Box 20, Folder 482)
  - Mathematical Sciences Research Institute (Box 20, Folder 483)
  - A.R.D. Mathias (Box 20, Folder 484)
  - Math-Physics Group Information (Box 20, Folder 485)
  - Bernard Meltzer (Box 20, Folder 486)
  - Memorial Service for David Martin Carter (Box 20, Folder 487)
  - Telis Menas (Box 20, Folder 488)
  - Telis Menas (Box 20, Folder 488A)
  - Elliott Mendelson (Box 20, Folder 489)
  - R. Bruce Merrifield (Box 20, Folder 490)
  - George Metakides (Box 20, Folder 491)
  - Elaine Michetti (Box 20, Folder 492)
  - Microcassettes (Box 20, Folder 493)
  - George Miller (Box 20, Folder 494)
  - I. Miller (Box 20, Folder 495)
  - Miscellaneous - Notes Dictated by Hao Wang on His Work, August 1984, Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 496)
  - MIT Press (Box 20, Folder 497)
  - William J. Mitchell (Box 20, Folder 498)
  - William J. Mitchell (Box 20, Folder 498A)
  - Modern Logic (Box 20, Folder 499)
  - The Monist (Box 20, Folder 500)
  - Ray Monk (Box 20, Folder 501)
  - Edward Moore (Box 20, Folder 502)
  - Stanford Moore Tribute Symposium (Box 20, Folder 503)
  - Gadi Moran (Box 20, Folder 504)
  - Sidney Morgenbesser (Box 20, Folder 505)
  - Oskar Morgenstern (Box 20, Folder 506)
  - Douglass B. Morris (Box 20, Folder 507)
  - Douglass B. Morris (Box 20, Folder 507A)
  - Yiannis Moschovakis (Box 20, Folder 508)
  - Stuart Moss (Box 20, Folder 509)
  - Ian B. Mueller (Box 21, Folder 510)
  - Ian B. Mueller (Box 21, Folder 510A)
  - Gert H. Müller (Box 21, Folder 511)
  - Music Books (Box 21, Folder 512)
  - Jan Mycielski (Box 21, Folder 513)
  - John Myhill (Box 21, Folder 514)
  - Wayne C. Myrvold (Box 21, Folder 515)
  - N (Box 21, Folder 516)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 21, Folder 517)
  - National Humanities Center (Prof. William Bennett) (Box 21, Folder 518)
  - National Science Foundation, Grant Proposals and Ratings (Box 21, Folder 519)
  - National Science Foundation, Grant Proposals and Ratings (Box 21, Folder 519A)
  - Robert Navon (Box 21, Folder 520)
  - R.J. Nelson (Box 21, Folder 521)
  - New York Academy of Sciences (Box 21, Folder 522)
  - New York City - Travel Information - The Rockefeller University Guide to New York, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 523)
  - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center (Box 21, Folder 524)
  - New York Science and Technology Foundation (Box 21, Folder 525)
  - New York Telephone (Box 21, Folder 526)
  - New York Times - Letter to the Editor: "Chinese Food Conquering the World" by Hao Wang, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 527)
  - New York University (Box 21, Folder 528)
  - Ninth International Congress on Thrombosis and Haemostasis (Box 21, Folder 529)
  - Ephraim Nissan (Box 21, Folder 530)
  - Eric D. Nix (Box 21, Folder 531)
  - Nadia Nogueira (Box 21, Folder 532)
  - Nadia Nogueira (Box 21, Folder 532A)
  - North-Holland Publishing Co. (Box 21, Folder 533)
  - Notre Dame (Box 21, Folder 534)
  - "Nous" (Box 21, Folder 535)
  - Nacek Nowaczek (Box 21, Folder 536)
  - O (Box 21, Folder 537)
  - Anthony G. Oettinger (Box 22, Folder 538)
  - Office Fire, November 1992 (Box 22, Folder 539)
  - Sue Olson (Box 22, Folder 540)
  - "On Computabilism: Some Subproblems" for Behavior and Brain Sciences (Box 22, Folder 541)
  - Open Court (Box 22, Folder 542)
  - Outside Work (Box 22, Folder 543)
  - Oxford University Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 544)
  - Oxford University Press (Box 22, Folder 545)
  - P (Box 22, Folder 546)
  - H. Pachale (Box 22, Folder 547)
  - Pacific Press Service (Box 22, Folder 548)
  - Heinz Pagels (Box 22, Folder 549)
  - D. Pager (Box 22, Folder 550)
  - Lowell J. Paige (Box 22, Folder 551)
  - PALLAS (Box 22, Folder 552)
  - Victor Pambuccian (Box 22, Folder 553)
  - Cedric Pan (Box 22, Folder 554)
  - Seymour A. Papert (Box 22, Folder 555)
  - Seymour A. Papert (Box 22, Folder 555A)
  - J.B. Paris (Box 22, Folder 556)
  - Charles D. Parsons (Box 22, Folder 557)
  - Charles D. Parsons (Box 22, Folder 557A)
  - Jacek Paśniczek (Box 22, Folder 558)
  - John Passmore (Box 22, Folder 559)
  - Solomon Passy (Box 22, Folder 560)
  - George W. Patterson (Box 22, Folder 561)
  - Peter Pavlicek (Box 22, Folder 562)
  - James Peck (Box 22, Folder 563)
  - Lorenzo Peña (Box 22, Folder 564)
  - Pending (Box 22, Folder 565)
  - Roger Penrose (Box 22, Folder 566)
  - Uwe Petersen (Box 22, Folder 567)
  - Franklin P. Peterson (Box 22, Folder 568)
  - P.P. Petkov (Box 22, Folder 569)
  - The Philosopher's Annual (Box 22, Folder 570)
  - The Philosopher's Index (Box 23, Folder 571)
  - "Philosophia" (Box 23, Folder 572)
  - Philosophica Mathematica, "On Physicalism and Algorithmism: Can Machines Think?" (Box 23, Folder 573)
  - Philosophia Verlag (Box 23, Folder 574)
  - "The Philosophical Review" (Box 23, Folder 575)
  - "Philosophy East and West" (Box 23, Folder 576)
  - Philosophy of Science (Box 23, Folder 577)
  - K.K. Phua (Box 23, Folder 578)
  - The Charles S. Pierce Newsletter (Box 23, Folder 579)
  - David F. Pincus (Box 23, Folder 580)
  - Plenum Publishing Corporation (Box 23, Folder 581)
  - Politikens Forlag (Box 23, Folder 582)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn (Box 23, Folder 583)
  - Gropal Prasad (Box 23, Folder 584)
  - Graham Priest (Box 23, Folder 585)
  - Arthur Prior (Box 23, Folder 586)
  - Professional Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 587)
  - Zhao-Min Pu (Box 23, Folder 588)
  - Publication Correspondence, 1954, 1967, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 589)
  - Gabriel Pustel (Box 23, Folder 590)
  - Hilary Putnam (Box 23, Folder 591)
  - Quine Conference, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 592)
  - W. Van Quine (Box 23, Folder 593)
  - R (Box 23, Folder 594)
  - Michael Rabin (Box 23, Folder 595)
  - Vaclav Rajlich (Box 23, Folder 596)
  - Recommendations (Box 23, Folder 597)
  - Edward Reich (Box 24, Folder 598)
  - D. Reidel Publishing Company (Box 24, Folder 599)
  - Report of Lectures, Publications, Work in Progress, Future Research (Box 24, Folder 600)
  - Retrospective Indexing Project (Box 24, Folder 601)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Humanities Fellowships (Box 24, Folder 602)
  - Rockefeller University Archives, Renée Mastrocco (Box 24, Folder 603)
  - Rockefeller University, Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Hall (Box 24, Folder 604)
  - Rockefeller University, Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Hall - Room Confirmation Letters (Box 24, Folder 605)
  - Rockefeller University, Academic Council (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 606)
  - Rockefeller University, Academic Council (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 607)
  - Rockefeller University, Allocations from the Biomedical Research Support Grant (Box 24, Folder 608)
  - Rockefeller University, David Baltimore, Includes: “Computer Theorem Proving and Artificial Intelligence” by Hao Wang “The Formal and the Intuitive in the Biological Sciences” by Hao Wang “Gödel and Einstein as Companions” by Hao Wang (Box 24, Folder 609)
  - Rockefeller University, Frank Brink, Jr. (Box 24, Folder 610)
  - Rockefeller University, Buildings and Grounds (Box 24, Folder 611)
  - Rockefeller University, Calendar of Events (Box 24, Folder 612)
  - Rockefeller University, Christmas Party Announcements (Box 24, Folder 613)
  - Rockefeller University, Committee of Lectures and Research Colloquia (Box 24, Folder 614)
  - Rockefeller University, Committee on Logic, Mathematics, and Philosophy (Box 24, Folder 615)
  - Rockefeller University, Computing Services (Box 24, Folder 616)
  - Rockefeller University, Consultation Policy (Box 24, Folder 617)
  - Rockefeller University, Controller's Office (Box 25, Folder 618)
  - Rockefeller University, Dean's Office (Box 25, Folder 619)
  - Rockefeller University, Development Office (Box 25, Folder 620)
  - Rockefeller University, Roger C. Elliot (Box 25, Folder 621)
  - Rockefeller University, Employee Health Office (Box 25, Folder 622)
  - Rockefeller University, Employee's Representative Committee (Box 25, Folder 623)
  - Rockefeller University, Faculty Administration (Box 25, Folder 624)
  - Rockefeller University, Faculty Appointments - Questionnaire (Box 25, Folder 625)
  - Rockefeller University, Faculty Records (Box 25, Folder 626)
  - Rockefeller University, Field Research Center (Box 25, Folder 627)
  - Rockefeller University, Flexible Spending Accounts (Box 25, Folder 628)
  - Rockefeller University, Foreign Faculty and Student Advisor (Box 25, Folder 629)
  - Rockefeller University, General Correspondence, 1965-1974 (Box 25, Folder 630)
  - Rockefeller University, General Correspondence, 1965-1974 (Box 25, Folder 630A)
  - Rockefeller University, General Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 25, Folder 631)
  - Rockefeller University, General Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 25, Folder 631A)
  - Rockefeller University, Graduate Fellow Lists (Box 25, Folder 632)
  - Rockefeller University, Graduate Program Applications (Box 25, Folder 633)
  - Rockefeller University, Grant Application Deadlines (Box 25, Folder 634)
  - Rockefeller University, Grant Overexpenditures (Box 25, Folder 635)
  - Rockefeller University, Grants (Small Awards) (Box 25, Folder 636)
  - Rockefeller University, Graphic Services (Box 25, Folder 637)
  - Rockefeller University, Guide for Graduate Students (Box 25, Folder 638)
  - Rockefeller University, Guide for the Preparation of Doctoral Theses (Box 25, Folder 639)
  - Rockefeller University, Housing Office (Box 25, Folder 640)
  - Rockefeller University, Institutional Review Board (Box 25, Folder 641)
  - Rockefeller University, International Exchanges (Box 25, Folder 642)
  - Rockefeller University, Judicial Committee (Box 25, Folder 643)
  - Rockefeller University, Laboratory Animal Research Center, Animal Rights Demonstration (Box 25, Folder 644)
  - Rockefeller University, Laboratory Safety (Box 25, Folder 645)
  - Rockefeller University, Lecture Halls Use (Box 25, Folder 645A)
  - Rockefeller University Logic Conference, May 13-14, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 646)
  - Rockefeller University, David J. Lyons (Box 25, Folder 647)
  - Rockefeller University, Mailroom (Box 25, Folder 648)
  - Rockefeller University, Maps (Box 25, Folder 649)
  - Rockefeller University, Alexander Mauro (Box 25, Folder 650)
  - Rockefeller University, MD-PhD Program (Box 25, Folder 651)
  - Rockefeller University, Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 652)
  - Rockefeller University, Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 652A)
  - Rockefeller University, New York City Clean Indoor Air Act (Box 26, Folder 653)
  - Rockefeller University, "News and Notes" (Box 26, Folder 654)
  - Rockefeller University, Rodney W. Nichols (Box 26, Folder 655)
  - Rockefeller University, Parking (Box 26, Folder 656)
  - Rockefeller University, Patent Policy (Box 26, Folder 657)
  - Rockefeller University, Personal Computers - Servicing (Box 26, Folder 658)
  - Rockefeller University, Pharmacy (Box 26, Folder 659)
  - Rockefeller University, Photocopy Service - Library (Box 26, Folder 660)
  - Rockefeller University, Plant Operations (Box 26, Folder 661)
  - Rockefeller University, Policies Governing Appointments and Promotions, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 662)
  - Rockefeller University, Policy on Industrial Sponsorship of Research (Box 26, Folder 663)
  - Rockefeller University, Public Affairs Office (Box 26, Folder 664)
  - Rockefeller University, Purchasing (Box 26, Folder 665)
  - Rockefeller University, Recycling Program (Box 26, Folder 666)
  - Rockefeller University, "Research Profiles" (Box 26, Folder 667)
  - Rockefeller University, Rockefeller Archive Center (Box 26, Folder 668)
  - Rockefeller University, David Rockefeller (Box 26, Folder 669)
  - Rockefeller University, Rockefollies, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 670)
  - Rockefeller University, Rockefollies, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 671)
  - Rockefeller University, Rockefollies, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 672)
  - Rockefeller University, Rockefollies, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 673)
  - Rockefeller University, Room Assignments (Box 26, Folder 674)
  - Rockefeller University, RU Press (Box 26, Folder 675)
  - Rockefeller University, RU Revue, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 676)
  - Rockefeller University, Judy Schwartz (Box 27, Folder 677)
  - Rockefeller University, Search Committees (Box 27, Folder 678)
  - Rockefeller University, Security (Box 27, Folder 679)
  - Rockefeller University, Senate (1 of 3) (Box 27, Folder 680)
  - Rockefeller University, Senate (2 of 3) (Box 27, Folder 681)
  - Rockefeller University, Senate (3 of 3) (Box 27, Folder 682)
  - Rockefeller University, Seven Springs (Box 27, Folder 683)
  - Rockefeller University, Substance Abuse Policy (Box 27, Folder 684)
  - Rockefeller University, Telephones (Box 27, Folder 685)
  - Rockefeller University, The Rockefeller University Review, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 686)
  - Rockefeller University, Thesis Instructions (Box 28, Folder 687)
  - Rockefeller University, Travel Information (Box 28, Folder 688)
  - Rockefeller University, Tri-Institutional Noon Recitals (Box 28, Folder 689)
  - Rockefeller University Women's Association (Box 28, Folder 690)
  - Rockefeller University, Richard Young (Box 28, Folder 691)
  - Francisco Rodriguez-Consuegra (Box 28, Folder 692)
  - Rolf Schock Prize (Box 28, Folder 693)
  - Robert Rosenberg (Box 28, Folder 694)
  - Gian-Carlo Rota (Box 28, Folder 695)
  - Lord Rothschild (Box 28, Folder 696)
  - Routledge and Kegan Paul (Box 28, Folder 697)
  - F. Rowbottom (Box 28, Folder 698)
  - Rudolf v.B. Rucker (Box 28, Folder 699)
  - Horst Ruthrof (Box 28, Folder 700)
  - S (Box 28, Folder 701)
  - G.E. Sacks (Box 28, Folder 702)
  - Samuel Sadikario (Box 28, Folder 703)
  - Gershon Sageev (Box 28, Folder 704)
  - Andrei Sakharov (Box 28, Folder 705)
  - Gerry Salton (Box 28, Folder 706)
  - Hidemitsu Sayeki (Box 28, Folder 707)
  - Cullen Schaffer (Box 28, Folder 708)
  - Roger Schank (Box 28, Folder 709)